Guide to the Ernie O'Malley Papers AIA.060
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series XV. Printed Ephemera, 1789-1950
  - O'Sullivan, Sean: prints and various protraits by, 1929-1939 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - O'Sullivan, Sean print: Portrait of Douglas Hyde, reprinted by The Irish Press, Christmas, 1938 (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - Pamphlet: What is Happening in France by Isabel Brown. Published by the Anti-Fascist Relief Committee, London, undated (Box 27, Folder 71)
  - "The Path of the Hangman" (illustration) by A.M. Cay; verso poem "Where is the Flag of England?", 1916 (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Postcards: Spain, Bruges, Le Port du Cehval, undated (Box 27, Folder 73)
  - Preface cover of publication; woodcut by Alan Odle, undated (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Print: "Der Seestrum" [The Storm] unknown artist; printed by A. Felgner, Berlin, Lith v. Buscheck, undated (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Print: "Grand Entry of the Sovereigns into Paris" on the 31 March 1814 by R. Boywer (color engraving) 1 Pall Mall [London], 1816 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Print: "Inside View of the Royal Stock Exchange at London," Thomas Bowles, color engraving, circa mid-18th century, undated (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Print: Untitled [study of female nude], charcoal drawing, reprinted in conte color from 1812 original, undated (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - Print in color: Wofle Tone by New Ireland Assurance Company, printed at the Signg of the Three Candles, Dublin, circa 1935-1945 (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - Prints: (items 16-72 through 16-78: Untitled [Four Courts Dublin], 16-77: The Four Law Courts, Dublin; 16-78: The Law Courts [Four Courts Dublin], late 18th century, undated (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - Rebel Cork's Fighting Story, 1947 (Box 42, Folder 27)
  - [Sketch of Dress Designs] Plates SVI, "No. 19 - Cantilly, Musee Conde" by unknown, circa 1930-1940 (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - Songs from "The Four Winds of Eirinn" by Ethna Carberry, signed and dated by Ernie O'Malley, 1919 (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - Stationery: Card, Cuala Press, circa 1940s (Box 27, Folder 44)
  - Stationery: Card with reproduction of a Paul Henry painting (blank inside), circa 1940-1949 (Box 27, Folder 39)
  - "View of Proach Patrick" by Augustus John (reprint in publication), undated (Box 27, Folder 70)
  - Walker, Charles: Correspondence to Mr. Starkey, Jan 29, 1907 (Box 27, Folder 57)
  - Yeats, William Butler: Correspondence to Mr. MacCartan (photocopy), undated (Box 27, Folder 56)
  - Yeats, William Butler, photoprint of portrait by Sean O'Sullivan, circa 1920 (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - Unprocessed Printed Ephemera Addition [envelopes, lists] (I), undated (Box 42, Folder 25)
  - Unprocessed Printed Ephemera Addition [envelopes, lists] (II), undated (Box 42, Folder 26)